Guide to the Richard Foreman and Kate Manheim Papers MSS.152
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series III: Production Materials
  - Subseries B: Richard Foreman's directorial works
    - "Three Acts of Recognition" by Botho Strauss. New York Shakespeare Festival Showbill., 1982 (Box 29, Folder 1319)
    - "Three Acts of Recognition" by Botho Strauss. Press., 1982 (Box 29, Folder 1320)
    - "Three Acts of Recognition" by Botho Strauss. Memorabilia., 1982 (Box 29, Folder 1321)
    - "Ma vie, ma mort..." by Kathy Acker, Italian translation by Enzo Siciliano., undated (Box 29, Folder 1311)
    - "Ma vie, ma mort..." by Kathy Acker. French translation by Kate Manheim and Noel Burch., undated (Box 29, Folder 1312)
    - "Stages" by Stuart Ostrow. Belasco Theatre playbill and tickets., 1978 (Box 29, Folder 1313)
    - "Stages" by Stuart Ostrow. Administrative materials including schedule, House seat order pad, contact sheet., 1978 (Box 29, Folder 1314)
    - "Stages" by Stuart Ostrow. Heavily annotated script., undated (Box 29, Folder 1315)
    - "Stages" by Stuart Ostrow. Press., 1978 (Box 29, Folder 1316)
    - "Stages" by Stuart Ostrow. Memorabilia., 1978 (Box 29, Folder 1317)
    - "Three Acts of Recognition" by Botho Strauss. Publicity., 1982 (Box 29, Folder 1318)
    - "Three Acts of Recognition" by Botho Strauss. New York Shakespeare Festival Showbill., 1982 (Box 29, Folder 1319)
    - "Three Acts of Recognition" by Botho Strauss. Press., 1982 (Box 29, Folder 1320)
    - "Three Penny Opera" by Brecht. New York Shakespeare Festival Lincoln Center playbill., 1976 (Box 29, Folder 1321)
    - "Three Penny Opera" by Brecht. New York Shakespeare Festival Central Park program, 1977 (Box 29, Folder 1322)
    - "Three Penny Opera" by Brecht. Program note from Joseph Papp regarding the new translation by Ralph Namheim and John Willett., undated (Box 29, Folder 1323)
    - "Three Penny Opera" by Brecht. Opinion in arbitration beteween Actors Equity Association and the New York Shapekspeare Festival., 1976 (Box 29, Folder 1325)
    - "Three Penny Opera" by Brecht. Documentation of Richard Foreman's dues to the Society of Stage Directors and Choreographers., 1976-1977 (Box 29, Folder 1326)
    - "Three Penny Opera" by Brecht. Press., 1975-1977 (Box 29, Folder 1327)
    - "Three Penny Opera" by Brecht. Press: "Yale/Theatre" Fall 1976, "Plays and Players" July 1976, "The Nation" May 1976, "Cue" August 1976. ["The Nation" is on acidic paper] (Box 29, Folder 1328)
    - "Three Penny Opera" by Brecht. Memorabilia, 1976 (Box 29, Folder 1329A)
    - Letter to Joe Papp from Tennessee Williams praising Richard Foreman's "Three-Penny Opera", 1976 (Box 29, Folder 1329B)
    - "Venus" by Suzan-Lori Parks. Public Theatre stagebill., 1996 (Box 29, Folder 1331)
    - "Venus" by Suzan-Lori Parks. Yale Repertory Theatre program., undated (Box 29, Folder 1332)
    - "Venus" by Suzan-Lori Parks. Press, 1996 (Box 29, Folder 1333)
    - "Venus" by Suzan-Lori Parks. Press: "Time" 23 Dec. 1996, "The New Yorker" 20 May 1996, "Time Out New York" 8 May 1996 (Box 29, Folder 1334)
    - "Where's Dick?" music by Stewart Wallace, libretto by Michael Korie. Program from Spring Opera Festival, Houston., 1989 (Box 29, Folder 1336)
    - "Where's Dick?" music by Stewart Wallace, libretto by Michael Korie. Press., 1989 (Box 29, Folder 1337)
    - "Woyzeck" by Georg Buchner. Hartford Stage programs, 1990 (Box 29, Folder 1338)
    - "Woyzeck" by Georg Buchner. Memorabilia: letter from Don Shewey, ticket., 1990 (Box 29, Folder 1339)
    - "Woyzeck" by Georg Buchner. Press., 1990 (Box 29, Folder 1340)
  - Subseries C: Other artist's productions of Richard Foreman plays
    - "Africanus Instructus" directed by Roy Brocksmith at the Lenox Arts Center, Stockbridge, MA. Press., 1984 (Box 30, Folder 1341)
    - "Eddie goes to Poetry City" directed by Greg Dean at Zocalo Theatre, Houston. Press., 1996 (Box 30, Folder 1342)
    - "Egyptology" Japanese production publicity flyers., undated (Box 30, Folder 1343)
    - "Egyptology" Japanese production memorabilia: photo booklet., undated (Box 30, Folder 1344)
    - "Film is Evil" production directed by Graham Paul at Warren Wilson College. Production file includes publicity, correspondence, reviews and program. [Student response papers], 1998 (Box 30, Folder 1345)
    - "Hotel for Criminals" directed by William Turner at Theatre Express. Program., undated (Box 30, Folder 1347)
    - "Lava" and "Breath" directed by Al Sgro. Son of Semele Ensemble atTheatre/Theater in Hollywood, CA. Press reviews and image., 2001 (Box 30, Folder 1348)
    - "Lines of Vision" directed by Lawrence Kornfeld at St. Clement's,New York, NY. Review., undated (Box 30, Folder 1349)
    - "The Mind King" directed by Koichi Makigami at P3 art and environment space, Japan. Reviews, program and publicity., 1995 (Box 30, Folder 1350)
    - "My Head was a Sledgehammer" directed by Max Lyandvert, Company B at Belvoir St Theatre, Sydney., 2001 (Box 30, Folder 1351)
    - No Strings Attached: A celebration of Richard Foreman, playwright. Festival staged a number of Foreman plays including "Angelface" directed by Richard Eoin Nash-Siedlecki, "Book of Splendors, Part I" directed by Michael John Garces, "Cafe Amerique" directed by Ian Hill, "Classical Therapy" directed by Jen Owens, "The Cure" directed by Tanya Kane-Parry, "Eddie goes to Poetry City" directed by Edward Einhorn, "Egyptology" directed by Ian W. Hill, "Film is Evil: Radio is Good" directed by Ian Hill, "Georges Bataille's Bathrobe" directed by Yelena Gluzman, "I've got the Shakes" directed by Susan Johnston, "The Mind King" directed by Emma Griffin, "Pain(t)" directed by Jamie Marcu, "Pandering to the Masses" directed by Jamie Marcu, "Penguin Touquet" directed by Daniel Kleinfeld, "Rhoda in Potatoland" directed by Aaron Beall, "Total Recall" directed by Margaret Cino, "Vertical Mobility" directed by Nancy Rogers. Programs., 1997 (Box 30, Folder 1352)
    - No Strings Attached festival, press., 1997 (Box 30, Folder 1353)
    - "Now that Communism is Dead" Japanese production, press., 2001 (Box 30, Folder 1354)
    - "Paradise Hotel" radio broadcast. Directed by Ben Popken at KVCU Radio 1190AM, University of Colorado, Boulder.Letter., 2002 (Box 30, Folder 1355)
    - "Permanent Brain Damage" directed by Takeshi Kawamura at Theater/Tops, Japan.Publicity flyer., 1997-1998 (Box 30, Folder 1356)
    - "Radio (Wisom)=Sophia" directed by Crystal Field at Theatre for the New City., undated (Box 30, Folder 1357)
    - "Samuel's Major Problems" directed by Jerry Mouawad at Imago, Portland Oregon. Publicity materials, press, images, 1996 (Box 30, Folder 1358)
    - "Slight" directed by Stuart Sherman at Playwrights Group Festival 3. Press, programs and script., 1977 (Box 30, Folder 1360)
    - "Symphony of Rats" directed by Jerry Mouawad at Imago in Portland, Oregon. Publicity materials and press., 1997 (Box 30, Folder 1361A)
    - "Walled Garden: (language)" directed by Bennett Theissen. Creation Theater Company at Inroads on Mercer St., New York City. Publicity postcard and program., 1982 (Box 30, Folder 1362)
  - Subseries D: Miscellaneous
    - Plastic spiral bound booklet of summaries, treatments and outlines to several of Richard Foreman's plays., undated (Box 30, Folder 1363)
    - Foamboard with sound cues. Unknown production., undated (Box 30, Folder 1364)
    - Unknown stage diagram, undated (Box 30, Folder 1365)
    - "Sets" unspecified production. Part I, undated (Box 30, Folder 1370)
    - "Sets" unspecified productions. Part II, undated (Box 30, Folder 1371)
    - "Sets" sketches and notes. part 1 of 2, undated (Box 30, Folder 1372)
    - "Sets" sketches and notes. part 2 of 2., undated (Box 30, Folder 1373)
    - "Recent Scenic" drawings and notes., undated (Box 30, Folder 1374)
    - Scrapbook pages, primarily press coverage of Richard Foreman's plays. [preservation concerns include glue and acidic paper.], undated (Box 30, Folder 1375)
    - Clippings removed from binder., undated (Box 30, Folder 1376)
    - Collected reviews, undated (Box 30, Folder 1377)
- Series IV: Photographs
  Subseries A: Photographs of Richard Foreman's Productions, includes photographs documenting Richard Foreman's productions including plays he wrote and directed, performance pieces, and his direction of other artist's work. Subseries B: Photographs of Richard Foreman, contains images of Richard Foreman including portraits, commercial images, and candid photographs associated with his professional career. Subseries C: Photographs of Performance Events, documents unscripted performance events such as "The Telephone Event".
  - Subseries A: Photographs of Richard Foreman's productions.
    - "Africanus Instructus" black and white contact sheets. Photographs by Babette Mangolte., 1986 (Box 30, Folder 1378)
    - "Bad Boy Nietzsche" 7 pages of black and white contact sheets, pre-production. Photographs by Paula Court., 1999 (Box 30, Folder 1379)
    - "Bad Boy Nietzsche" 8 pages of black and white contact sheets. Photographs by Paula Court., 2000 (Box 30, Folder 1380)
    - "Bad Boy Nietzsche" 12 pages, 187 color slides. Photographs by Paula Court., undated (Box 30, Folder 1381)
    - "Benita Canova" 10 pages of black and white contact sheets. Photographs by Paula Court., 1998 (Box 30, Folder 1382)
    - "Benita Canova" 9 pages of black and white contact sheets. Photographs by T. Charles Erickson. 28 January 1998. (Box 30, Folder 1383)
    - "Benita Canova" 3 pages of color slides. Photographs by T. Charles Erickson., 1998 (Box 30, Folder 1384)
    - "The Birth of the Poet" 6 pages of black and white prints. 11 pages color photographs of production materials. Photographs by Leo van Velzen, Rotterdam., 1984 (Box 30, Folder 1386)
    - "Birth of the Poet" 9 pages of black and white contact sheets of BAM Next Wave theater festival production. Photographs by Beatriz Schiller., 1985 (Box 30, Folder 1387)
    - "Birth of the Poet" 1 black and white contact sheet. Photographs by Paula Court., 1990 (Box 30, Folder 1388)
    - "Book of Splendors" [no part designation] two black and white prints by Jean Kalman, Paris., undated (Box 30, Folder 1389)
    - "Book of Splendors I" 22 black and white prints by Babette Mangolte, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 1391)
    - "Book of Splendors II" 6 pages of black and white contact sheets and four 4x5 black and white negatives. Photographs by Lois Greenfield., undated (Box 30, Folder 1392)
    - "Book of Splendors II" black and white print by Photos Lespes, Paris., undated (Box 30, Folder 1393)
    - "Book of Splendors II" 4 black and white prints by Richard Levine., undated (Box 30, Folder 1394)
    - "Book of Splendors II" 29 black and white prints by Babette Mangolte., undated (Box 30, Folder 1395)
    - "Book of Splendors II" 19 black and white prints and two 4x5 negatives by Babette Mangolte., undated (Box 30, Folder 1396)
    - "Book of Splendors II" three 5x7 prints by an unknown photographer., undated (Box 30, Folder 1397)
    - "Book of Splendors II" 26 duplicate photographs mounted on cards to look like stereoscopic photographs. Unknown photographer, labeled "CB" on card reverse. Part 1 of 2., undated (Box 30, Folder 1398)
    - "Book of Splendors II" 27 duplicate photographs mounted on cards to look like stereoscopic photographs. Unknown photographer, labeled "CB" on card reverse. Part 2 of 2., undated (Box 30, Folder 1399)
    - "Blvd de Paris" 3 black and white contact sheets by Johan Elbers., undated (Box 30, Folder 1400)
    - "Blvd de Paris" 4 black and white contact sheets by Lois Greenfield., undated (Box 30, Folder 1401)
    - "Blvd de Paris" 24 black and white contact sheets by Babette Mangolte., 1977 (Box 30, Folder 1402)
    - "Blvd de Paris" 16 black and white prints by Babette Mangolte., 1977 (Box 31, Folder 1403)
    - "Blvd de Paris" 10 black and white prints mounted on brown construction paper with blue envelope. Photographed by Fracois Thiolat., undated (Box 31, Folder 1404)
    - "Blvd de Paris" 14 black and white contact sheets and three black and white prints by Nathaneil Tileston, 1977 (Box 31, Folder 1405)
    - "Cafe Amerique" black and white contact sheets assembled into a booklet. Agence de Presse Bernard, Paris., undated (Box 31, Folder 1407)
    - "Cafe Amerique" 4 black and white prints by Enguerand, Paris., 1981 (Box 31, Folder 1408)
    - "Cafe Amerique" 1 black and qute print by Martine Loubet, Paris., undated (Box 31, Folder 1409)
    - "Cafe Amerique" 11 contact sheets and 3 prints by Nicolas Treatt, Paris. Black and white as well as color. (Box 31, Folder 1410)
    - "Classical Therapy" 13 black and white prints sheets by Babette Mangolte, 1973 (Box 31, Folder 1413)
    - "The Cure" 8 black and white contact sheets and 3 black and white prints by Nancy Campbell., undated (Box 31, Folder 1414)
    - "The Cure" 2 black and white contact sheets amd 3 black and white prints by Panela Duffy., 1986 (Box 31, Folder 1415)
    - "The Cure" 2 black and white prints by Pamela Duffy, with letter from Paula Court., 1995 (Box 31, Folder 1417)
    - "The Cure" 5 black and white contact sheets and 5 black and white prints by Babette Mangolte, 1986 (Box 31, Folder 1418)
    - "The Cure" Black and white negatives and contact sheets, roll 1, 20 May 1986 by Craig Massey. (Box 31, Folder 1419)
    - "The Cure" black and white negatives and contact sheets, roll 2, 20 May 1986 by Craig Massey. (Box 31, Folder 1420)
    - "The Cure" black and white negatives and contact sheets, roll 3, 20 May 1986 by Craig Massey. (Box 31, Folder 1421)
    - "The Cure" black and white negatives and contact sheets, Roll 4, 20 May 1986 by Craig Massey. (Box 31, Folder 1422)
    - "The Cure" black and white negatives and contact sheets, Roll 5, 20 May 1986 by Craig Massey. (Box 31, Folder 1423)
    - "The Cure" black and white negatives and contact sheets, Roll 6, 20 May 1986 by Craig Massey. (Box 31, Folder 1424)
    - "The Cure" black and white negatives and contact sheets, Roll 7, 20 May 1986 by Craig Massey. (Box 31, Folder 1425)
    - "The Cure" black and white negatives, unlabeled, Craig Massey., undated (Box 31, Folder 1426)
    - "The Cure" photo-related list, unknown, undated (Box 31, Folder 1427)
    - "The Cure" black and white print by unknown photographer., undated (Box 31, Folder 1428)
    - "Dr Faustus Lights the Lights" 8 black and white prints by Pierre-Olivier Deschamps, Paris., undated (Box 31, Folder 1429)
    - "Dr Faustus Lights the Lights" 1 black and white print by Enguerand, Paris., 1982 (Box 31, Folder 1430)
    - "Dr. Faustus Lights the Lights" 3 black and white contact sheets, 24 black and white prints by Anne Nordmann, Paris., undated (Box 31, Folder 1431)
    - "Dr Faustus Lights the Lights" 3 photographs by Erika Rablau, Berlin., undated (Box 31, Folder 1432)
    - "Dr Selavy's Magic Theater" 3 black and white contact sheets, photographer unknown., 1984 (Box 31, Folder 1434)
    - "Don Juan" three black and white prints by unknown photographer., undated (Box 31, Folder 1435)
    - "Don Juan" one color print by Craig Massey, undated (Box 31, Folder 1436)
    - "Eddie goes to Poetry City" 7 black and white contact sheets by Paula Court., 1991 (Box 31, Folder 1437)
    - "Eddie Goes to Poetry City" 2 black and white prints and 1 black and white contact sheet by Paula Court. Images of Richard Foreman on the "Eddie" set., 1990 (Box 31, Folder 1438)
    - "Eddie goes to Poetry City" 6 photocopies of black and white images by Paula Court., 1991 (Box 31, Folder 1439)
    - "Eddie goes to Poetry City" 8 color slides by George Mott., 1991 (Box 31, Folder 1440)
    - "Eddie Goes to Poetry City" 6 black and white contact sheets and 4 black and white prints by Martha Swope., 1991 (Box 31, Folder 1441)
    - "Eddie Goes to Poetry City" Seattle production. 36 black and white 3.5x5 prints., undated (Box 31, Folder 1442)
    - "Egyptology" 6 black and white prints by Martha Swope., 1983 (Box 31, Folder 1443)
    - "Egyptology" 7 black and white prints by Martha Swope., 1985 (Box 31, Folder 1444)
    - "Elephant Steps" 1 black and white print by Clemens Kalischer, Stockbridge MA., undated (Box 31, Folder 1445)
    - "Evidence" 20 black and white prints by Babette Mangolte., undated (Box 31, Folder 1446)
    - "Evidence" black and white contact sheet by unknown photographer., undated (Box 31, Folder 1448)
    - "The Fall of the House of Usher" 2 black and white contact sheets by Beatriz Schiller, New York., 1989 (Box 31, Folder 1449)
    - "The Fall of the House of Usher" 7 black and white prints by Teatro Comunale di Firenze, Italy., undated (Box 31, Folder 1450)
    - "Film is Evil..." cast photo, undated (Box 31, Folder 1451)
    - "Film is Evil..." 5 black and white contact sheets and 1 black and white print by Nancy Campbell., undated (Box 31, Folder 1452)
    - "Film is Evil..." 7 black and white contact sheets and 1 black and white print by Babette Mangolte., 1987 (Box 31, Folder 1453)
    - "Film is Evil..." 6 black and white contact sheets by Martha Swope, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 1454)
    - "Film is Evil..." 2 black and white prints by Martha Swope., 1991 (Box 31, Folder 1455)
    - "Die Fledermaus" 2 black and white prints from Theatre National de L'Opera de Paris., undated (Box 31, Folder 1456)
    - "Die Fledermaus" black and white contact sheet by Nicolas Treatt, undated (Box 31, Folder 1457)
    - "Die Fledermaus" 1 black and white print with annotations, 9 color contact sheet. Unknown photographer(s), undated (Box 31, Folder 1458)
    - "George Bataille's Bathrobe" 17 black and white contact sheets by Anne Nordmann, Paris., undated (Box 31, Folder 1459)
    - "George Bataille's Bathrobe" 15 black and white contact sheets by Anne Nordmann, Paris., undated (Box 31, Folder 1460)
    - "George Bataille's Bathrobe" 19 black and white prints by Anne Nordmann, Paris., undated (Box 31, Folder 1461)
    - "George Bataille's Bathrobe" 21 black and white prints by Anne Nordmann, Paris., undated (Box 31, Folder 1462)
    - "George Bataille's Bathrobe" 7 color contact sheets, 3 black and white contact sheets, 3 black and white prints by Nicolas Treatt, 1983 (Box 31, Folder 1463)
    - "The Golem" 5 black and white prints by Martha Swope Associates: Susan Cook., undated (Box 31, Folder 1464)
    - "Hotel China" 30 black and white prints by Babette Mangolte., undated (Box 31, Folder 1465)
    - "Hotel China" 30 black and white prints by Babette Mangolte., undated (Box 31, Folder 1466)
    - "Hotel China" 30 black and white prints by Babette Mangolte, undated (Box 31, Folder 1467)
    - "Hotel China" 30 black and white prints by Babette Mangolte., undated (Box 31, Folder 1468)
    - "Hotel China" 13 black and white prints by Babette Mangolte., undated (Box 31, Folder 1469)
    - "Hotel China" 9 black and white contact sheets by Peter Moore., 1972 (Box 31, Folder 1470)
    - "Hotel Fuck" or "Paradise Hotel" 19 color prints by Tina Barney., 1999 (Box 32, Folder 1472)
    - "Hotel Fuck" or "Paradise Hotel" 2 black and white contact sheets of Richard Foreman at rehersals by Paula Court., 1998 (Box 32, Folder 1473)
    - "Hotel Fuck" or "Paradise Hotel" 11 black and white contact sheets by Paula Court., 1999 (Box 32, Folder 1474)
    - "Hotel Fuck" or "Paradise Hotel" 7 color slides of Theater der Welt performance by Paula Court.., 1999 (Box 32, Folder 1475)
    - "Hotel Fuck" or "Paradise Hotel" 2 color photographs by Paula Court., undated (Box 32, Folder 1476)
    - "Hotel Fuck" or "Paradise Hotel" 3 black and white photographs by Paula Court., undated (Box 32, Folder 1477)
    - "Hotel Fuck" or "Paradise Hotel" 19 color slides by T Charles Erickson., undated (Box 32, Folder 1478)
    - "Hotel Fuck" or "Paradise Hotel" 2 black and white prints by unknown photographer and press review from Manuel Igrejas to Sophie Haviland., undated (Box 32, Folder 1479)
    - "Hotle Fuck" or "Paradise Hotel" 9 black and white prints for press use. Photo credits include T Charles Erickson and Paula Court. Includescaption and contact information for Manuel Igrejas., undated (Box 32, Folder 1480)
    - "I've Got the Shakes" 8 black and white contact sheets by Paula Court., 1995 (Box 32, Folder 1481)
    - "I've Got the Shakes" 6 black and white contact sheets by Brooke Williams., undated (Box 32, Folder 1482)
    - "I've Got the Shakes" 56 color slides on 4 pages by Brooke Williams., undated (Box 32, Folder 1483)
    - "King Cowboy Rufus..." 11 black and white contact sheets by Paula Court., 2004 (Box 32, Folder 1484)
    - "Lava" 4 black and white contact sheets, 7 black and white prints and 3 photocopies of prints by Paula Court. labeled "Early Rehersal and PR shots", undated (Box 32, Folder 1485)
    - "Lava" 8 black and white contact sheets, 2 black and white prints, and 1 photocopy of a print by Paula Court., 1989 (Box 32, Folder 1486)
    - "lava" 1 black and white contact sheet and 1 black and white print by C. M. Hardt., 1989 (Box 32, Folder 1487)
    - "Lava" 1 black and white print of Richard Foreman by Kate Manheim., undated (Box 32, Folder 1488)
    - "Lava" 19 color slides by George Mott., undated (Box 32, Folder 1489)
    - "Lava" 6 black and white prints by Susan Tobias., 1990 (Box 32, Folder 1490)
    - "Luogo+Bersaglio" 24 black and white prints and 2 large black and white negatives by Marcello Norberth., undated (Box 32, Folder 1491)
    - "Luogo+Bersaglio" 24 black and white prints by Marcello Norberth., undated (Box 32, Folder 1492)
    - "Luogo+Bersaglio" 6 black and white prints by Marcos Zimmerman, Rome., undated (Box 32, Folder 1493)
    - "Madness and Tranquility" 12 photographs on 9 pages, color and black and white. Images part of a study for a proposed dual role in the play: Kate Manheim as Mr. and Mrs. St Vitis., undated (Box 32, Folder 1494)
    - "Madness adn Tranquility" 20 black and white prints by unknown photographer(s)., undated (Box 32, Folder 1495)
    - "Madness and Tranquility" 15 black and white prints by Craig Massey., undated (Box 32, Folder 1496)
    - "Madness and Tranquility" 1 black and white contact sheet and 1 black and white print by Robert del Tredici., 1973 (Box 32, Folder 1497)
    - "Maria del Bosco" 9 black and white contact sheets by Paula Court., 2002 (Box 32, Folder 1500)
    - "Maria del Bosco" 3 black and whiet prints by Paula Court., undated (Box 32, Folder 1501)
    - "Mind King" 6 black and white contact sheets by Paula Court., 1992 (Box 32, Folder 1502)
    - "Mind King" 6 black and white prints by Paula Court., undated (Box 32, Folder 1503)
    - "Mind King" 7 black and white contact sheets by Babette Mangolte., 1992 (Box 32, Folder 1504)
    - "Mind King" 21 black and white prints by Babette Mangolte., 1992 (Box 32, Folder 1505)
    - "Mind King" 6 black and white prints by Babette Mangolte., 1992 (Box 32, Folder 1506)
    - "Miss Universal Happiness" 3 black and white contact sheets, 1 black and white print and several photocopies of images by Paula Court., 1985 (Box 32, Folder 1507)
    - "Miss Universal Happiness" 14 black and white contact sheets by Babette Mangolte., 1985 (Box 32, Folder 1508)
    - "Miss Universal Happiness" 11 black and white prints by Babette Mangolte., 1985 (Box 32, Folder 1509)
    - "Miss Universal Happiness" 2 black and white contact sheets by Beatriz Schiller., 1985 (Box 32, Folder 1510)
    - "My Head was a Sledgehammer" 10 black and white contact sheets by Paula Court., 1994 (Box 32, Folder 1511)
    - "My Head was a Sledgehammer" 2 black and white prints, 3 4x5 black and white negatives by Paula Court., 1994 (Box 32, Folder 1512)
    - "My Head was a Sledgehammer" 3 black and white prints by Paula Court returned by Bomb Magazine., undated (Box 32, Folder 1513)
    - "My Head was a Sledgehammer" 5 black and white prints by Heidrun Lohr and several color photocopy images from Australian production., undated (Box 32, Folder 1514)